<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zachary Baker</title>
    <link>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Zachary Baker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 18:52:32 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>An Innovative Criterion in Evaluating Bitcoin&#39;s Environmental Impact</title>
      <link>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/posts/bitcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 18:52:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/posts/bitcoin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zethernet</title>
      <link>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/posts/zethernet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 18:52:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/posts/zethernet/</guid>
      <description>Zethernet Go to this site to view Zethernet
About Zethernet is a Ethereum blockchain explorer. One of the pillars of a blockchain is the ability for anyone to view someone else&amp;rsquo;s transactions, account balance, and more. Zethernet allows you to do this. You can search by Ethereum address, transaction hash, block number, and more. Feel free to check out my address (zacbaker.eth) or anyone else&amp;rsquo;s. It&amp;rsquo;s all in real time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Library of Babble</title>
      <link>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/posts/babble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 18:52:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/posts/babble/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt; Library of Babble The Library of Babble &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The Library of Babble contains everything that has been written, will be written, and could be written. Well, at least things with a length of less than 856. The possible characters are the lowercase alphabet, the comma, the period, and the space. So how many books are there in this athenaeum? Well with 29 possible characters and ~855 characters in one book, there are 29^855 books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Encompas</title>
      <link>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/posts/encompas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 18:34:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/posts/encompas/</guid>
      <description>Encompas Go to encompas.tech to view our site which is hosted via GitHub Pages
Inspiration In a world where a persons values define how they live, being able to accurately determine your stance on world issues is vital. We immediately noticed that all the current quizzes that help determine your stance are extremely outdated, vague, or inaccurate.
What it does Encompas allows users to vizualize where they stand on the political compass via a 4d graph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Effect of Location on Number of Lyme Disease Cases</title>
      <link>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/posts/lyme-disease/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 21:25:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/posts/lyme-disease/</guid>
      <description>The Effect of Location on Number of Lyme Disease Cases By Zachary R. Baker and Srishanth Tangedipalli Thomas Jefferson High School for Science and Technology Dr. Kathleen Morrow, Ms. Erinn Harris, and Ms. Julia Litchford
Introduction Lyme Disease has had over 25,000 cases every year in the US since 2007 (Monaghan et al, 2015). It is a vector-borne disease, which means that it is transmitted to humans and other animals by blood-feeding animals, such as ticks or mosquitos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2023 Goals</title>
      <link>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/2023goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/2023goals/</guid>
      <description>2023 Goals (Week of January 2nd) Daily Read/listen to The Bible Read at least 10 pages of another book Duolingo Code/Commit to Github Weekly Lift four times Erg 5 times Run 7 miles Swim once Year-Long No apple devices Arch linux 33 ACT 6:49 2k </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Email: zac.r.baker06@gmail.com 2024zbaker@tjhsst.edu Phone Number: 1-703-405-1525 Github: zacbakerr LinkedIn: Zac Baker Public Key: GPG zacbaker.eth </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading Log</title>
      <link>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/readinglog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/readinglog/</guid>
      <description>Reading Log Title Author Finished The Bible Various Authors TBD The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn Mark Twain TBD Narrative of the Life of Frederick Douglass, an American Slave Frederick Douglass November 17th, 2022 The Scarlet Letter Nathaniel Hawthorne October 13th, 2022 Permanent Record Edward Snowden Sep 12th, 2022 Ramayana Valmiki May 19th, 2022 Things Fall Apart Chinua Achebe May 6th, 2022 Strange Case of Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde Robert Louis Stevenson March 21st, 2022 Home of the Gentry Ivan Turgenev Febuary 17th, 2022 Frankenstein Mary Shelly January 18th, 2022 47 Ronin John Allyn November 30th, 2021 Inferno Dante Alighieri October 25th, 2021 The Canterbury Tales: Fragment III Geoffrey Chaucer September 9th, 2021 Oedipus the King Sophocles September 2nd, 2021 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zacbakerr.github.io/zacsite/resume/</guid>
      <description>I am a junior at Thomas Jefferson High School for Science and Technology Extracurriculars Junior Year Activity Role Class Council Historian TJ Crew Rower Resilient Crew Rower TJ Speech Officer TJ Media Photographer, Cinematographer Angler&amp;rsquo;s Alliance Treasurer Sophomore Summer Activity Role Blockchain Research with Georgetown&amp;rsquo;s Professor Matuso Intern Resilient Crew Rower Zeed (Investment Startup) Website Developer Sophomore Year Activity Role Class Council Historian TJ Speech Officer Sysadmin Understudy Inspirit AI Ambassador TJ Crew Coxswain (Men&amp;rsquo;s First Varsity Boat) TJ Media Photographer, Cinematographer Freshman Summer Activity Role NOVA Speech Academy Counselor Inspirit AI Ambassador Freshman Year Activity Role Froshcomm1 Officer Class Council Officer TJ Crew Coxswain (Men&amp;rsquo;s First Novice Boat) TJ Media Photographer, Cinematographer TJ Speech Member Anthos Capital Intern Other Extracurriculars Chess Club Long time casual player.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
